<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Porch Documentation</title>
    <link>http://localhost:8080/porch/index.html</link>
    <description>Porch - A Portable Process Orchestration Framework porch is a sophisticated Go-based process orchestration framework designed for running and managing complex command workflows. It provides a flexible, YAML-driven approach to define, compose, and execute command chains with advanced flow control, parallel processing, and comprehensive error handling.&#xA;It was designed to solve the problem of orchestrating complex command workflows in a portable and easy-to-use manner. Its portability means that you can confidently run the same workflows locally, in CI/CD pipelines, or on any server without worrying about compatibility issues.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:8080/porch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/porch/basics/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/porch/basics/index.html</guid>
      <description>Getting Started with Porch This section covers the fundamental concepts you need to understand before building workflows with Porch.&#xA;Why Use Porch? Porch was designed to solve several common challenges in command orchestration:&#xA;Portability Run the same workflows across different environments:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commands</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/porch/commands/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/porch/commands/index.html</guid>
      <description>Command Types Porch provides six built-in command types for different execution patterns. Each command type serves a specific purpose and has its own configuration options.&#xA;Overview Command Type Purpose Execution Mode Shell Execute shell commands Single PowerShell Execute PowerShell scripts Single Serial Run commands sequentially Container Parallel Run commands concurrently Container ForEach Directory Execute commands in multiple directories Container Copy to Temp Copy working directory to temporary location Utility Single Commands Single commands execute a single task:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Output Control</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/porch/output/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/porch/output/index.html</guid>
      <description>Controlling Output Porch provides several ways to control the output and logging behavior of your workflows. This includes environment variables for logging, command-line flags for output formatting, and color control.&#xA;Log Levels Porch uses structured logging with different log levels. Control the log level using the LOG_LEVEL environment variable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminal User Interface (TUI)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/porch/tui/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/porch/tui/index.html</guid>
      <description>Terminal User Interface (TUI) Porch includes a real-time Terminal User Interface (TUI) that provides live progress monitoring during command execution. The TUI offers better visibility into complex workflows compared to traditional text-based output.&#xA;Enabling the TUI Use one of these flags to enable the TUI:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Topics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/porch/advanced/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/porch/advanced/index.html</guid>
      <description>Advanced Topics This section covers advanced features and implementation details of Porch.&#xA;Topics Circular Dependency Detection - Understanding command group validation TUI Implementation - Technical details of the TUI system</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>